This is far enough.
Thank you, Shintaro.
Escher, get ready.
Right!
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
Episode 22: Black Dragon
That's enough! Don't do it again!
Don't use your power again, Mumbles!
You hear me?!
Stop!
Stop
You dumb son of a bitch!
I got him! I saved the kid, Mumbles!
Come on!
Come on, man...
You gotta say something, Crow!
Dante! Could you help me?!
There's more incoming!
Is Bishop Dante not helping
because he's an enemy?
He's scary looking... Maybe he
really is working for him...?
Ever so sorry.
I wish I could help more, but...
Bruise from poison punch
It seems your love is... heftier,
than I expected, Ren.
That's not love! It's poison!
What is this bishop's deal?!
Miss. Do you know who's
responsible for this mess?
How about it?
H-How... How do I answer this?
Whatever!
I do.
The one responsible for what's happening...
Just like I thought.
His Luxa is a conjuration-type spell with
the traits of purifying-type sorcery.
The issue is the specifics
of that purification.
It has nothing to do with what
the gods would define as evil.
He's the one making the
distinction about what's evil.
And what is, consequently, purified.
Take a fireball, which ordinarily
wouldn't be effected by purification...
Should Guitane decide as such,
it becomes evil, and is purified.
Those symbols are likely an indicator.
I wonder what would happen if I came
in contact with the one for me...?
I'd like to know!
That said, the weaknesses are pretty clear.
One: it takes a few seconds
to alter the symbols.
Two: he can't create a symbol that
effects sorcery, in broad strokes.
If he could, he wouldn't need
to alter it to affect flame,
barriers, and divine sorcery specifically.
Three: it looks like all of the divine sorcery
symbols have been switched to flame.
So, does that mean he can only
use three types at once?
That chimera body was fascinating
enough, yet he goes as far as...
to tweak divine law—altering
the mana signature of the gods.
He truly is...
Abhowwent!
Kid. Can you make it to
the shelter on your own?
Yeah...
What about you?
I've got work to do.
Here's hoping you find your mom.
As for me, I can't ditch a pal.
What the hell do you think you're
doing, you smoky lizard?
I've had enough of your crap, asshole!
Everyone's in the clear, Crow!
You did it, man! Now we just gotta help you!
Get you back to the church
for a purification...!
Having a cheat power like
making his words reality...
obviously came with a hefty price!
Crow was coughing up blood
every time he used his power!
Look how big this damn thing is...
It's no wonder he pushing past his limits!
It must've been like trying to shove
a watermelon up his nose, every time!
But he looked so damn happy!
Happy being able to use his
powers to save people...!
What...
are you...
Laughing...?
You're dead, asshole.
This damned lizard... was laughing...
this whole time... at us... at Crow...
At everything Crow's been through!
Weird how just looking at him makes
the crap he's been through clear.
What's weirder is, how we just met today....
And we barely even talked...
But I already feel like we're best bros!
Bring it on!
Why would you do that?!
You're fighting me, got it?!
Hey!
He's already dead, damn you!
Not yet!
I can sense that Crow's still alive!
The twin bishops are gonna patch him up!
Crow's gang?
Sorry to trouble you when
you're exhausted, Tao, but...
I'm not tired! And I'm already doing it.
It's okay. I can't sense any civilians.
Crow's amazing!
He was able to protect
them all from this beast!
He was an amazing warrior.
But it also means that this enemy was so
strong that he could only hold it off...
Now, where do we begin?
How about I kick its butt,
and you go for its face?
No. I'll go for the rear,
you target the face.
No way! That mug's too freaky!
I get the butt!
Hyakkaken—
House of Langlis—
Wheeling Twin Dragons!
Unbelievable. This dragon...
it was targeting...!
My life flashed before my eyes! Again!
How many times is this gonna happen today?!
Tao! Your hand...
It's fine.
Stay focused! If we can't pull this
off, everything goes to waste!
Everything Crow...
Everything we all did!
This thing is enough to upend all of it!
I've realized something.
I'm sorry, Batts.
The boy... He's already...
There's no stopping the infernal wyrm.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
It was clear to me from
the moment of my birth.
The fact that I was a slave.
And that my lot in life would be to
fly around with this man on my back.
I would act as loyal as a dog,
as to not earn his displeasure,
and I flew with all my heart and soul.
And after a long, long trek
over the great sea...
Master Guisarme!
You've already grasped
how to teleport things!
My Master obtained the
greatest power in the world.
I was as proud as I was terrified.
He was my Master.
And no one could stop him anymore...
I think I'm done with this dragon, now.
I suppose detours can prove quite
fruitful, every once in a while.
I wonder how long Lordost Island
has been a den for devils?
He's a true monster.
The one inhabiting that manor...
Most likely the demon realm's nobility,
the so-called Demon Lords.
Who is that human?
This is Lord Guisarme's territory.
What do you suppose would happen if I
cast my Luma Maxima on a demon lord?
The light of purification has a
pronounced effect on his kind...
It would likely do substantial damage.
Aren't they afraid?
But what about his heart?
Do you suppose it would become "clean"?
The answer is no.
There is no purifying his heart.
Which is to say, there is no taint to it.
The hearts of monsters are pristine.
They mean no harm.
When they kill, or when they destroy,
or even when they abandon their comrades...
And I somehow realized...
That this would be my next master.
Please, put this chimera body
to use however you see fit.
Guitane... that was why I followed him.
It's my wish that you would use
it to seek out your true nature.
Over half of my body had been
replaced with different parts,
without a single change
to my dog-like mentality.
He could speak of my true nature, or freedom,
there was no way I could
understand any of that.
If you have nowhere to go,
you can come with me.
I'm preparing a rather grand event.
Although, I don't have much
planned beyond that.
I'm lost myself, you see.
I hope he finds his way.
As for me...
I think I'm beginning to understand...
who it is I am!
He's had giant arms grafted onto him!
This dragon is a chimera too!
We can't assume anything about it!
Tao?!
She took the full impact...
House of Langlis—
Double Tiger, Claw and Fang
Oh, this is so much fun.
They're so adorable.
Sylpha! Damn it!
Come on! I'm begging you!
You gotta heal him somehow!
All of you...
Those faces you make...
Batts! Let me treat your wounds!
You're hurt badly too!
Who cares about me?! This guy's a hero!
Your screams are what made it clear to me.
Where's it... aiming...?
The shelter?!
Screw you!
That I am strong...
And I am cruel...
Now...
Damn it... move, body!
More...
Let me feel it more!
I don't care... who does it...
God... or devil...!
As I bathe in your hatred...
I feel the ecstasy of domination!
Please, someone stop this forsaken dragon!
You did well to endure, good bishops.
We will take over from here.
I am going to focus on healing
this one. Will that suffice?
Works for me.
Make sure you save him.
Crow's part of the crew.
So, Black Dragon...
Where the hell do you get off?
Who?
Er... I'm, uh...
Right! The wandering adventurer! Grimtaro!
Grim...taro?
I gotta admit, he's got
quite the hottie aura.
What are those horns?
Grim, huh?
Friend or foe?
Nice guy!
Maybe it's not him?
These are just... accessories! For my hair!
This is so embarrassing!
Do you realize that if you
show up looking like that,
you're going to be mistaken
for a monster or a chimera?
Y-You got a point...
I changed forms like Jihriel said,
but it's so awkward trying to look human!
Regardless...
We're on your side. Crow's gonna be fine.
That blond guy, Jerkiel, is gonna save him.
Who are you calling Jerkiel?
But I will heal him.
Even a single fatality in this battle
would justify me to taking my own life.
Tao.
How do you know my—
There aren't any civvies around
here anymore, right?
All clear!
Then... let's raise some hell.
Hey.
You're not a pillbug. Quit rolling around.
I heard you laughing, y'know.
There's no way a black dragon from the
Netherworld came to the human realm on its own.
Bet you were a lap dragon
that got abandoned, huh?
Pitiful little bastard.
Hope you weren't counting on
me taking pity on you, though.
Survival of the fittest...
That's how it works in the Netherworld.
And you were trying play
by those rules up here...
making a mess of my turf.
No pride, no nothing... just a rowdy mutt
going nuts after getting off its chain.
And you have the nerve to laugh?
I can't even bring myself to kill you.
Tuck your tail between your legs and go home.
Th-That thing can fly?!
This demon...
is too kind!
After everything that's happened
to a wretch like me... he's still...
trying to show me how to live like a dragon.
Even now...
he grants me time I could use to escape.
Thank you... but I can't do that.
I can't turn my back on this
swell of emotions I feel.
I will live as a dragon...
and maybe die as one!
Not filled with joy or fear... but pride!
Waah
Having lived these many years...
with a draconic roar!
Dual incantation...
Arctis Obscura Forta Magnificat!
We all had our own baggage.
Were we all able to overcome our
regrets during this battle?
Lastly, please swallow this
sphere with Luma Maxima.
By activating it, your rotting bodies will
turn to dust, and your souls will be purified.
When would you want to use it?
A good question. If you're being
tortured in a way that's unbearable,
or if you have overcome your lingering
feelings for the world, and yearn to pass on.
Would that be betraying me?
Of course not.
I am simply using you all.
I don't consider you comrades.
I'm not so sure about that.
If nothing else, by meeting you, I was able
to die in a way fitting for a dragon.
So, I won't use your sphere.
Guitane... I'll be seeing you in Hell.
Gulp
Blop
I've been able to absorb a decent amount
of mana since the seal was broken.
I'm stronger!
Maybe I could take a demon lord now...!
Huh?
Nah, no way. Not yet, anyhow.
Which means...
I'm still nowhere close to that
brat up above the clouds, yet.
Come on. We'll get a glimpse
of the apex, together.
Sorry for the delay.
It's fine. How's Crow?
What kind of blast was that?!
He'll be fine. The worst part is over.
Hey! Where did that blond
Jerkiel fellow go?!
But I'm exhausted.
And can barely move anymore.
Look at how much better Crow looks!
The folks down there should
be fine at this point.
Right. And all we can do at this
point is offer unsolicited advice...
Let's get going. Up above the clouds...
To the final battle!
The name's Grimtaro! I'm an adventurer
who was just passing through.
All the notable bad guys are down!
That just leaves the last
battle, way up on high.
Next time, on episode 23:
"The Battle Above the Clouds."
Episode 23
The Battle Above the Clouds
You will witness the depths of sorcery.